glenwooddentalgroup.com 2010-06-15

# Privacy

At Intelligent Dental Marketing, Inc., your privacy is important to us. The following statement describes the privacy practices we use on our Web site. 

**COLLECTION AND USE OF INFORMATION** ****

Intelligent Dental Marketing collects information volunteered by the visitor in registering or participating in surveys, such as your name, address, telephone number, and practice name.  We use this information to administer our business activities, improve our Web site, provide customer service, and to make available other products and services to our customers and prospective customers.  We do not disclose your personally identifiable information to unaffiliated third parties for their independent use without your consent.  We may share your information with our agents or contractors in connection with services they perform for us, but we do not rent or sell our customer list. 

If you supply us with your street address, e-mail address or phone number, you may receive periodic mailings or calls from us with information about new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings or calls, you may "opt out" by writing, calling, or e-mailing us at the addresses listed below: 

Intelligent Dental Marketing, Inc. 

7138 South Highland Drive, 217 

Salt Lake City, UT 84121 

Phone: 1-877-942-8855 

E-mail: info@idmtools.com 

In addition to the information you volunteer, our web server automatically collects such information as the domain name of the site providing you with Internet access, the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet, your browser type and version, operating system and platform, the average time spent on our site, pages viewed, information searched for, access times and other relevant statistics.  We use this information in order to ensure that unauthorized users do not access the information on our site, and in the aggregate to measure the use of our site and to administer and improve our site. 

We also use cookies to provide visitors a personalized experience on our site. Cookies are pieces of information that a Web site transfers to the memory or hard drive of a visitor's computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies to allow access without re-entering the visitor's password, to make improvements, and to better tailor our site to our visitors' needs. We also use this information to verify that visitors meet the criteria required to process their requests. Most browsers used by visitors have options that allow the visitor to control whether the browser will accept cookies, reject cookies, or notify the visitor each time a cookie is sent, but setting a browser to reject cookies will prevent access to our site. In addition, you can delete your Intelligent Dental Marketing cookies from your browser program at any time. 

To the extent required or permitted by law, we may also collect, use and disclose personal information in connection with security related or law enforcement investigations or in the course of cooperating with authorities or complying with legal requirements. 

In the event you have any questions concerning this privacy statement or the information you have provided, you should contact: 

Intelligent Dental Marketing, Inc. 

7138 South Highland Drive, 217 

Salt Lake City, UT 84121 

Phone: 1-877-942-8855 

E-mail: info@idmtools.com 

**SECURITY** ****

We take commercially reasonable precautions to keep all information obtained from our online visitors secure against unauthorized access and use and we periodically review our security measures.  As noted in our Terms and Conditions, however, you are responsible for keeping your login information and passwords confidential.

**LINKS TO OTHER SITES** ****

Our site contains links to other Web sites. These sites are not covered by this privacy statement, and we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these other sites. 

**CHANGES TO THE POLICY** ****

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement and related business practices at any time by posting updated text on this site.  Please check this page periodically for updates. 

Last Updated: July 1, 2004, your privacy is important to us. The following statement describes the privacy practices we use on our Web site.
